The suits are heated on the train, like my booty is warm right now, it's the third world
country they like to call everywhere else.
Oh, free of the big palace, the Konbuk room is Thursday, so we can do that on Thursday.
Oh cool, okay.
So we're here at the palace, on the steps of the palace, oh my gosh, I feel like I'm
in one of the shows that I watch.
We're giving Joseon Era, we're giving Mesh Hat, we're giving Humbok Dress, we're giving some
of my favorite dramas, and I feel like I'm in them, I'm in, I'm in the drama of K.
Oh, what?
Oh, is it a dragon?
Yeah.
You go to like an old school cabinets that are like that?
Yes.
We jammin' in here with our what's it called?
We're jammin' with our what's it called?
Kalguk Su.
I like your lessons.
Support a real one.